[
    {
      "id": "03-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "03",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "01",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">なまえ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "名",
      "kanji_B": "前",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>名前<rt>なまえ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "03-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "03",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "02",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">くに</span>",
      "kanji_A": "国",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>国<rt>くに</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "03-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "03",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "03",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">わたし</span>",
      "kanji_A": "私",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>私<rt>わたし</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "04-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "04",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "04",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ちち</span>",
      "kanji_A": "父",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>父<rt>ちち</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "04-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "04",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "05",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">はは</span>",
      "kanji_A": "母",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>母<rt>はは</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "04-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "04",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "06",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">こ</span>ども",
      "kanji_A": "子",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>子<rt>こ</rt></ruby></span>ども",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "04-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "04",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "07",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">にほん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "日",
      "kanji_B": "本",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>日本<rt>にほん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "05-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "05",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "08",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">みず</span>",
      "kanji_A": "水",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>水<rt>みず</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "05-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "05",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "09",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">た</span>べます",
      "kanji_A": "食",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>食<rt>た</rt></ruby></span>べます",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "05-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "05",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "10",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">の</span>みます",
      "kanji_A": "飲",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>飲<rt>の</rt></ruby></span>みます",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "06-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "06",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "11",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">さかな</span>",
      "kanji_A": "魚",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>魚<rt>さかな</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "06-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "06",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "12",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">にく</span>",
      "kanji_A": "肉",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>肉<rt>にく</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "06-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "06",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "13",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">す</span>き（な）",
      "kanji_A": "好",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>好<rt>す</rt></ruby></span>き（な）",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "07-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "07",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "14",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">いえ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "家",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>家<rt>いえ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "07-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "07",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "15",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">あたら</span>しい",
      "kanji_A": "新",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>新<rt>あたら</rt></ruby></span>しい",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "07-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "07",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "16",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ひろ</span>い",
      "kanji_A": "広",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>広<rt>ひろ</rt></ruby></span>い",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "07-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "07",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "17",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ふる</span>い",
      "kanji_A": "古",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>古<rt>ふる</rt></ruby></span>い",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "08-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "08",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "18",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">うえ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "上",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>上<rt>うえ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "08-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "08",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "19",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">した</span>",
      "kanji_A": "下",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>下<rt>した</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "08-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "08",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "20",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">なか</span>",
      "kanji_A": "中",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>中<rt>なか</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "21",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">げつ</span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "kanji_A": "月",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>月<rt>げつ</rt></ruby></span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "22",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">か</span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "kanji_A": "火",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>火<rt>か</rt></ruby></span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "23",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">すい</span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "kanji_A": "水",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>水<rt>すい</rt></ruby></span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "24",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">もく</span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "kanji_A": "木",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>木<rt>もく</rt></ruby></span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "25",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">きん</span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "kanji_A": "金",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>金<rt>きん</rt></ruby></span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "26",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ど</span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "kanji_A": "土",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>土<rt>ど</rt></ruby></span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-007",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "27",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">にち</span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "kanji_A": "日",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>日<rt>にち</rt></ruby></span><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "09-05-008",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "09",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "28",
      "question_text": "<ruby>月<rt>げつ</rt></ruby><span class=\"text-deco-u\">ようび</span>",
      "kanji_A": "曜",
      "kanji_B": "日",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<ruby>月<rt>げつ</rt></ruby><span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>曜日<rt>ようび</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "10-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "10",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "29",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">あさ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "朝",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>朝<rt>あさ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "10",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "30",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ひる</span>",
      "kanji_A": "昼",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>昼<rt>ひる</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "10",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "31",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">よる</span>",
      "kanji_A": "夜",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>夜<rt>よる</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "10",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "32",
      "question_text": "10<span class=\"text-deco-u\">じ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "時",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "10<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>時<rt>じ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "10",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "33",
      "question_text": "15<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ふん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "分",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "15<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>分<rt>ふん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "10",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "34",
      "question_text": "12<ruby>時<rt>じ</rt></ruby><span class=\"text-deco-u\">はん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "半",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "12<ruby>時<rt>じ</rt></ruby><span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>半<rt>はん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "10-05-007",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "10",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "35",
      "question_text": "30<span class=\"text-deco-u\">まい</span>",
      "kanji_A": "枚",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "30<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>枚<rt>まい</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "11-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "11",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "36",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">よ</span>みます",
      "kanji_A": "読",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>読<rt>よ</rt></ruby></span>みます",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "11-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "11",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "37",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">き</span>きます",
      "kanji_A": "聞",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>聞<rt>き</rt></ruby></span>きます",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "11-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "11",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "38",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">み</span>ます",
      "kanji_A": "見",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>見<rt>み</rt></ruby></span>ます",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "11-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "11",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "39",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ほん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "本",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>本<rt>ほん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "11-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "11",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "40",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">とも</span>だち",
      "kanji_A": "友",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>友<rt>とも</rt></ruby></span>だち",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "11-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "11",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "41",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">なに</span>",
      "kanji_A": "何",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>何<rt>なに</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "12-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "12",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "42",
      "question_text": "2021<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ねん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "年",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "2021<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>年<rt>ねん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "12-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "12",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "43",
      "question_text": "12<span class=\"text-deco-u\">がつ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "月",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "12<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>月<rt>がつ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "12-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "12",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "44",
      "question_text": "31<span class=\"text-deco-u\">にち</span>",
      "kanji_A": "日",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "31<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>日<rt>にち</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "12-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "12",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "45",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">きょう</span>",
      "kanji_A": "今",
      "kanji_B": "日",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>今日<rt>きょう</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "12-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "12",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "46",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">こんしゅう</span>",
      "kanji_A": "今",
      "kanji_B": "週",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>今週<rt>こんしゅう</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "12-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "12",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "47",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">こんど</span>",
      "kanji_A": "今",
      "kanji_B": "度",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>今度<rt>こんど</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "48",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ひがし</span>",
      "kanji_A": "東",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>東<rt>ひがし</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "49",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">にし</span>",
      "kanji_A": "西",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>西<rt>にし</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "50",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">みなみ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "南",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>南<rt>みなみ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "51",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">きた</span>",
      "kanji_A": "北",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>北<rt>きた</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "52",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">かいしゃ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "会",
      "kanji_B": "社",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>会社<rt>かいしゃ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "53",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">き</span>ます",
      "kanji_A": "来",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>来<rt>き</rt></ruby></span>ます",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-007",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "54",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">い</span>きます",
      "kanji_A": "行",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>行<rt>い</rt></ruby></span>きます",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "13-05-008",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "13",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "55",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">の</span>ります",
      "kanji_A": "乗",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>乗<rt>の</rt></ruby></span>ります",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "14-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "14",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "56",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">おお</span>きい",
      "kanji_A": "大",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>大<rt>おお</rt></ruby></span>きい",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "14-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "14",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "57",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ちい</span>さい",
      "kanji_A": "小",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>小<rt>ちい</rt></ruby></span>さい",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "14-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "14",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "58",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">たか</span>い",
      "kanji_A": "高",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>高<rt>たか</rt></ruby></span>い",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "14-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "14",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "59",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ひく</span>い",
      "kanji_A": "低",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>低<rt>ひく</rt></ruby></span>い",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "14-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "14",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "60",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">まえ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "前",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>前<rt>まえ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "14-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "14",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "61",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">うし</span>ろ",
      "kanji_A": "後",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>後<rt>うし</rt></ruby></span>ろ",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "14-05-007",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "14",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "62",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">よこ</span>",
      "kanji_A": "横",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>横<rt>よこ</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "15-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "15",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "63",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">いりぐち</span>",
      "kanji_A": "入",
      "kanji_B": "口",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>入口<rt>いりぐち</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "15-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "15",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "64",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">でぐち</span>",
      "kanji_A": "出",
      "kanji_B": "口",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>出口<rt>でぐち</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "15-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "15",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "65",
      "question_text": "２<span class=\"text-deco-u\">かい</span>",
      "kanji_A": "階",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "２<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>階<rt>かい</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "15-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "15",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "66",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">お</span>す",
      "kanji_A": "押",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>押<rt>お</rt></ruby></span>す",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "15-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "15",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "67",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ひ</span>く",
      "kanji_A": "引",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>引<rt>ひ</rt></ruby></span>く",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "15-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "15",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "68",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">やす</span>い",
      "kanji_A": "安",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>安<rt>やす</rt></ruby></span>い",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "69",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">いち</span>",
      "kanji_A": "一",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>一<rt>いち</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "70",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">に</span>",
      "kanji_A": "二",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>二<rt>に</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "71",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">さん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "三",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>三<rt>さん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "72",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">よん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "四",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>四<rt>よん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "73",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ご</span>",
      "kanji_A": "五",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>五<rt>ご</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "74",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ろく</span>",
      "kanji_A": "六",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>六<rt>ろく</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-007",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "75",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">なな</span>",
      "kanji_A": "七",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>七<rt>なな</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-008",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "76",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">はち</span>",
      "kanji_A": "八",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>八<rt>はち</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-009",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "77",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">きゅう</span>",
      "kanji_A": "九",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>九<rt>きゅう</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "16-05-010",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "16",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "78",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">じゅう</span>",
      "kanji_A": "十",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>十<rt>じゅう</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "79",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">ひゃく</span>",
      "kanji_A": "百",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>百<rt>ひゃく</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "80",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">せん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "千",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>千<rt>せん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "81",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">まん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "万",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>万<rt>まん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "82",
      "question_text": "300<span class=\"text-deco-u\">えん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "円",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "300<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>円<rt>えん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "83",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">やす</span>み",
      "kanji_A": "休",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>休<rt>やす</rt></ruby></span>み",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "84",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">えいが</span>",
      "kanji_A": "映",
      "kanji_B": "画",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>映画<rt>えいが</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-007",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "85",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">にほんご</span>",
      "kanji_A": "日",
      "kanji_B": "本",
      "kanji_C": "語",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>日本語<rt>にほんご</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-008",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "86",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">べんきょう</span>します",
      "kanji_A": "勉",
      "kanji_B": "強",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>勉強<rt>べんきょう</rt></ruby></span>します",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "17-05-009",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "17",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "87",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">か</span>います",
      "kanji_A": "買",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>買<rt>か</rt></ruby></span>います",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "18-05-001",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "18",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "88",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">おんせん</span>",
      "kanji_A": "温",
      "kanji_B": "泉",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>温泉<rt>おんせん</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "18-05-002",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "18",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "89",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">よてい</span>",
      "kanji_A": "予",
      "kanji_B": "定",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>予定<rt>よてい</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "18-05-003",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "18",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "90",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">らいしゅう</span>",
      "kanji_A": "来",
      "kanji_B": "週",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>来週<rt>らいしゅう</rt></ruby></span>",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "18-05-004",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "18",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "91",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">あ</span>います",
      "kanji_A": "会",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>会<rt>あ</rt></ruby></span>います",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "18-05-005",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "18",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "92",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">はい</span>ります",
      "kanji_A": "入",
      "kanji_B": "",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>入<rt>はい</rt></ruby></span>ります",
      "number_of_blank": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "18-05-006",
      "practice_type_id": "05",
      "lesson_id": "18",
      "category_id": "02",
      "question_id": "93",
      "question_text": "<span class=\"text-deco-u\">りょこう</span>します",
      "kanji_A": "旅",
      "kanji_B": "行",
      "kanji_C": "",
      "kanji_D": "",
      "answer": "<span class=\"text-deco-u text-em\"><ruby>旅行<rt>りょこう</rt></ruby></span>します",
      "number_of_blank": 2
    }
  ]